

# **Muhammet Enes Çetin**

Nationality: Turkish Date of birth: 2001 Phone number: (+90) 5442817369

Email address: enespcetin@gmail.com

in LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/muhammet-enes-cetin-35112b279

**Website:** <a href="https://github.com/enesctnn">https://github.com/enesctnn</a>

• Home: (Türkiye)

#### **ABOUT ME**

I graduated from Ankara University Computer Programming in 2022. I am currently developing Frontend Web applications using HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Reactjs and Nextjs14 using TypeScript technologies. You may visit <a href="https://github.com/enesctnn">https://github.com/enesctnn</a> for the websites I developed in these languages. Every step I took in the software, every new information I learned and needed to learn, made me even more curious, and I look forward to learning new things. As a Frontend Web developer, I love researching and reading documentation. I also have (beginner-intermediate) level knowledge of Adobe's Photoshop, After Effects and Premiere Pro technologies.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Front End Web Developer (INTERNSHIP)

**MINISTRY OF AGRICULTURE AND FORESTRY** [ 26/04/2023 - 28/12/2023 ]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye | Website: https://www.ogm.gov.tr/tr

I produced Javascript and React projects under the supervision of Orbis Project manager Ahmet Yatcı at the General Directorate of Agriculture and Forestry also uploaded them on my Github repositories. I had the opportunity to observe teamwork and functioning. Ahmet Yatcı, Tel No: +90 505 864 67 53 . Beştepe, Söğütözü Cd. 8/1, 06560 Yenimahalle/Ankara.

#### **Computer Programming (INTERNSHIP)**

**Atatürk Forest Farm (AOC)** [ 16/08/2021 – 15/09/2021 ]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye | Website: www.aoc.gov.tr

We provided technical support to AOC employees during internship. We solved problems such as formatting computers, updating/downloading softwares that (completing-correcting) connection between AOC server and the computer and sometimes by replacing the broken cable.

I have experienced a good team work, friendship and partnership under the same roof.

#### AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN INTERNSHIP

**Turkish Aerospace Industries TUSAŞ** [ 10/12/2016 – 13/06/2019 ]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye | Website: https://www.tusas.com

I did an internship at TUSAŞ as an Aircraft Maintenance Technician. My responsibilities were; to support our team for assambling the frame of T-129 Attack Chopper we have faced with couple duties such as combine the pieces with sealant and make sure around of the piece clean at the same time. I also maintained and supply the aircraft pieces such as gearbox and engine cover at Universal Lathe Machine.

### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Front-End Web Developement / Reactjs Nextjs / Javascript HTML CSS / Good listener and communicator / Adobe (After Effects, Premiere Pro, Photoshop) / Team-work oriented

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

# **Computer Programming**

**Ankara University** [ 31/08/2020 – 13/06/2022 ]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye | Website: <a href="https://www.ankara.edu.tr/dizin/myo/">https://www.ankara.edu.tr/dizin/myo/</a> | Final grade: 3,8/4

## Aircraft Airframe, Engine and Maintenance

**Private Ankara Darüşşifa Technical Anatolian Vocational School** [ 15/09/2016 – 14/06/2019 ]

City: Ankara | Country: Türkiye | Website: <a href="http://www.darussifa.com.tr/">http://www.darussifa.com.tr/</a> | Final grade: 82,53/100

#### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Turkish

Other language(s):

**English** 

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2** 

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

THIS RESUME WAS CREATED TO BE PRESENTED ON PERSONAL WEBSITE ON THE SPECIFIED DATE 30/04/2024